happened
[music]
Hello Hello Welcome to 2200 time Today we
can directly buy long but Indian exam
ICICI Lombard, which is the
largest private insurance company in India, is
believed to buy
Indian company Indian Subscribe 9 inch
This company Subscribe In 2016,
they were in talks with Reliance, but the deal could
not be finalized, but now the school is going to reach a
very good high level,
now we are seeing
that Indian, who was struggling earlier, will get
a good deal with her boss and will
qualify for the final
ICICI Lombard and
all the insurance will be present, if we look at the
net profit of ICICI Lombard, its product company,
if we reduce its group, then
it has reduced
by 5.2 times and the reason for this is that at this
time, if we talk about life insurance policy at the time of Pandu, then due to
Indian
Subscribe school, the
pressure on the company is increasing.  And the company is continuously
falling into loss, it will be a very
good and very beneficial that the
Indian company should come out and improve its situation,
one more thing is that people are
buying because if we talk about
ICICI Lombard, it is very good, it is continuously
falling, a good company, if
we see it today also, then the price of it has
created frustration yesterday, but if we look at it then we do
not like that company much,
if this bill is passed or not, it will depend on the subscription,
if you like our video then
definitely like it and tell us in the comment section
how you liked this video,
subscribe so that you get to know
all the finance related news information
and definitely press the bell icon